Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise.
Every time dangerous, dangerous.
We like it serious, serious, oh.
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go.
The balls built between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know.
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones we love.
We'll carry on till we see the light.
The sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core.
Is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go.
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know.
That's what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Yes, we've got
superpowers.
Yes, we're the Super Bowers!
How else would Straw Hat be
using your ability, stupid?
Okay, this mirror is the key
for the allied forces to escape.
And when I fulfill this task,
I can get my heart back.
Once I'm squared away, it's
payback time for Caesar.
I wonder how everything is going.
I didn't hear Big Mom's quack.
What's keeping the old bag?
So far, so good.
The cake's everywhere.
The feral gaggle of straw
hats are amassing chaos.
Mother Carmel's picture is shattered.
Come on, why hasn't
she blown a gasket yet?
What could be the holdup?
Luffy, wait. Listen to me.
Tread carefully.
Big Mom is having an emotional
overload and can't focus,
so we must show her the
picture again. Sure!
If you say so, that's what we'll do!
Just leave it to me!
Stop Straw Hart!
Don't let him get near Mama!
Why are you sabotaging us?
Veggie!
You two-faced bastard.
Need lead, Katakuri.
I'm so mad!
You traitor!
I knew that you would turn on us.
Hey, Press. Hmm?
Hurry up and slaughter them already.
I'm getting to it.
So impatient.
My brother wants me to
wrap this up lickety-split.
He gets antsy since he sees the future,
but he's not the only one who
knows what will happen this time.
Considering that you're
currently trapped in candy,
you'll die frozen here
in place, tears and all.
Coo-coo-coo, there's no other outcome.
You bastard, if I had my raid suit, then
we would be the ones laughing at you!
What is that?
A weapon?
Did you think that would help?
I don't think so
How sad.
You tried to sneak a weapon into your
own son's wedding and got caught.
Leave now, Reiju!
Great, it's you again.
Don't get in my way!
That jackass.
What is he doing anyway?
Sticking his nose in our mess.
Sanji
I underestimated your kind nature.
Even now you won't abandon us.
Despite our rejection of you.
I've lived my entire life in shame
because i was a fin smoke however.
Seeing you all grown up
i feel a sense of peace.
A conscience still remains
in our family's bloodline.
Thank you sanji.
This isn't good.
His family needs help.
Don't let it touch you!
Go on!
Thanks, Pedro!
Now 5,000 brick fish!
Attack!
Veggie!
She ain't held, Katakuri!
Not so fast!
Mama...
Mama, no!
Mother!
Ugh!
Mama!
Showtime!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Okay, I know you can't hear me, but we're
going to leave the rest up to you guys!
No, Mama, she's hurt.
That's the stuff.
Somebody!
We have to stop Veggie and this man!
Hurry!
You traitor!
How dare you!
You'll pay for this!
Hey, Big Mom!
She in hell!
Mother...
Please, answer me, mother.
No one listens.
They don't want to hear
what I have to say.
Hey, mother, where did you go?
Her feelings overflow.
The memories that bring
forth these tears began
63 years ago on an
island in the New World.
This is a kingdom inhabited by giants.
the home of the warriors of Elbaf.
Now come along, sweetie.
Where are we?
I'll tell you all about this place later.
Why don't you come on down, Lin-Lin?
Okay!
Here we go!
Hey! Hey!
This is new!
So what are we doing here, anyway?
Daddy has an important
job on a nearby island.
Lin-Lin, will you be a good
girl and wait for us here?
Aww!
I want to go, too!
What if I told you you could have all the
treats in your bag while you stay put?
What?
What daddy said.
Oh, love, love.
Oh, wait, right here.
Take your time. OK?
Bye-bye.
I'll be right here when you get back.
It's OK, honey. Don't worry.
After all the damage she's caused,
we're lucky it's just deportation.
She's far too much for us to handle.
They say the Holy Mother lives here.
I just know she'll save Limping.
We've got to head out!
This island is dangerous as hell!
See you later!
Wow!
What big fishies those are!
This is weird.
When are they coming back?
I'm getting really hungry.
Hey, mama, papa, where did you both go?
It's taking you so long.
In regards to Elbath,
it was once home to giant warriors
who struck fear into the heart of the.
world a century ago.
They were known as the Giant Pirates.
These ruthless titans wreaked
havoc on the seas and land alike,
destroying everything in their path.
However,
their reign of terror
abruptly ended when the two
captains of the Giant Pirates
suddenly vanished one day
and passed into legend.
Directionists, after the
loss of their leaders,
the remaining stragglers
Of their crew were
rounded up by the navy and
sentenced to execution.
Wait
a
moment.
Halt the execution!
Heaven requires forgiveness, not wrath.
Unexpectedly, a beautiful
wandering none appeared.
Her name was Sister Carmel.
Why show them mercy?
Do you not realize how much terror
these nuisances have caused us?
Even more reason then?
Why can't you see that
if you kill those men the warriors
of Albac will seek vengeance?
You would be endangering all of humankind.
Please, forgive their sins.
I vow to show them the way.
I will guide them to a brighter world,
where all people can join
hands and laugh together.
Soon enough,
she came to be known as Mother Carmel
and founded the House of Lambs,
an orphanage that took in children
with no other place to go,
regardless of their race or class.
Settling in the homeland
of these colossal beings,
she also worked as a diplomatic bridge
between giant kind and humanity.
And then, 37 years later...
You're in good hands now, Lin-Lin.
I'll take perfect care of you until
your mommy and daddy return here.
They ain't coming back.
You're never gonna leave us.
You'll find that the children
here are rather unique.
Yeah, unique enough to dump.
You'll fit in quite nicely.
Uh-huh. Thanks, lady.
You got anything to eat?
You're a big one.
Are you a giant?
Let's go fix you up some food, then.
Come on.
The orphanage inhabitants
included an exiled prince,
an impoverished boy who was
nearly so old into slavery.
and various problem children whose
parents were unable to control them.
They all lived a peaceful
life among the giants,
where their past could
not haunt them any longer.
Hey, Mother!
Who's the new girl? Huh? Ah!
But most important of all,
for a child who is always
bigger than everyone around her,
The land of Elbaf was the first place
Lin-Lin had ever seen where the people,
houses, and everything else fit her size.
It was a comforting place for her.
Wowie!
So cool!
Oh, no!
What happened?
Oh, what's the matter, Lin-Lin, dear?
A bear and a wolf were being
mean to each other in the forest.
I was only trying to
tell them it's not nice
to fight and that they should be friends.
So I put them in the same cage
so they could make up. But Mr.
Bear must have gotten
hungry and ate Mr. Wolf.
So I smacked him for being bad.
Mr.
Bear looks sorry to me.
How much did you hit him?
Just one time.
She killed the bear with a single blow.
Oh, what a sweetie you are.
You only wanted those two to
become friends, didn't you?
You're such a kind-hearted girl.
Uh-huh.
How about we go find the
other kids so we can play?
Yeah.
For the first time in Lin-Lin's
life, someone finally understood her.
I saw it!
Lin-Lin killed a bear with only one punch!
That girl's way scary!
Did you hear?
Barry the Giant's hurt.
She tried to smack a
mosquito off of the poor guy.
We heard a bunch of his bones go snap!
Knock it off!
What'd you do?
Lin-Lin! Yes, Mother?
Please, she's hurting me!
Did you ever notice he has an extra elbow?
I thought it'd be nice to
straighten it out for him.
No, don't!
He's from the Longarm tribe.
That's natural for him.
Oh, I didn't know.
Lin-Lin, no!
What are you doing?
He's got weird fins, so I thought
I'd help by tearing him off.
Sweetheart, please stop!
He's a fish man.
It's normal for him to have fish parts.
Oh, really?
I was so scared.
Everyone, please forgive her.
Lin-Lin always means well.
Mother Carmel always preached forgiveness.
Wait for me!
Lin-Lin's gonna get away!
Stop running away!
After 10 months of residing in
the mighty country of Elbaf,
the warriors of the land
accepted Lin-Lin with open arms.
Can you believe it's been 40 years?
Ever heard of a duel lasting that long?
I can't say that I have.
Let's go pick him up after
another decade or so.
Hey, Lin-Lin!
Time's running out.
You finished getting ready?
Buddy?
What do you mean, Kashi?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Your first time, huh?
In Elbaf, we fast for 12 days straight
right before the Winter Solstice Festival.
What's fast mean?
We won't eat any food.
Plus, the only thing
we can drink is water.
It's gonna start tomorrow.
But I'll be so hungry!
Yeah, but once it's all
done, we'll have a big feast!
Your true opponents, yourself.
Now stand up, Hiradine.
This giant boy, Hyrodine,
grew up to be one of the Coliseum fighters
Luffy faced off against in Dressrosa.
However, they weren't enemies for long.
He, along with the other
Grateful Gladiators,
pledged allegiance to
Luffy over a cup of sake.
He is now a proud member
of the Straw Hat fleet.
He's so tough! Ready!
Listen,
either Chief Dory or Chief Brogy will
return to revive the giant pirate crew.
You must be prepared for when that
day finally arrives you're a warrior.
Hone your skills Hardeen
Chief Beardfall Chief
Beardhill I know Carmel
preaches trade over plunder
That's well and good.
But we are still warriors above all else.
We can't let our blades dull. Yeah.
Yes, I understand, sir.
You're so cool.
No wonder why all the giants
look up to our chiefs.
I want to be a great warrior
like them when I grow up.
And to what do we owe the
honor of your visit today?
We're here to eat Semla in the village and
to fetch the children
at the House of Lambs.
Would you care to join us, Lin-Lin?
What's a semla?
It's a sweet and delicious
treat! Yeah? Give me some!
Before the big fast, we get lots
of nutrition by eating semla!
So it's yummy like a candy or cake?
And we're gonna eat it right now?
Yeah!
It's a tasty cream dolloped and a dessert
bread with marzipan topped
with powdered sugar!
It's the best before the fast!
It's awesome, haven't we?
May the feast commence.
Let us celebrate the recent
birth of Prince Loki.
And also, let's raise a barrel to the
village newborns Rodo and Goldberg.
We praise the sun above.
May it shine over them warmly.
To the sun!
Thank you so much for the food, sun!
Simla!
We have plenty, so don't hold back.
So...
so...
It's sweet!
Now that's yummy!
I'm so happy!
Whoa, Midland, slow down!
You need to save some for the other kids
or there won't be enough to go around.
Take your time.
You must show the sun some gratitude.
You are similar!
Oh, God!
I can't stop!
I love you, similar!
Mother, please.
I feel like I'm gonna starve and die.
The Winter Solstice Festival
celebrates the sun's death rebirth
you must be strong after a
harsh winter it will regain its
strength and shine down on us
again the more that we suffer
the deeper our gratitude to the
sun becomes fortitude hang in
there kids.
Well, if Mother says so,
then I'll keep at it.
I'm losing weight.
You really
aren't.
Just look at me.
I'm withering away.
Linlin, dear.
You're doing wonderfully.
Just Just a little more to go.
Lin-Lin had really taken
a liking to Mother Carmel.
I'm hungry.
I want some more, some more.
I...
wanna eat it... again.
Mother, help!
Quick, the trouble!
What happened, Carrot dear?
Lin-Lin's crazy!
Oh no!
What did you do?
Lin-Lin!
Give it to me right now!
I want to!
The village of Elpa was
destroyed by that girl!
This is a nightmare!
You've made a dire mistake lately.
What right do you have to thank the sun?
Even a child can only be forgiven so much.
Chief, your rule!
Give me Samba!
Poor Samba!
Mother Carmen, I'm sorry.
That is no little girl standing
before us. Don't do it!
Chief, your rule!
She's a god of disaster!
Samba!